{
    "categories": [],
    "description": "Translate these British words into their American equivalents.",
    "difficulty": -1,
    "questions": [{
        "answer": "Soccer",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Football"
    }, {
        "answer": "Fries",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Chips"
    }, {
        "answer": "Chips",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Crisps"
    }, {
        "answer": "Bathroom",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Loo"
    }, {
        "answer": "Gas",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Petrol"
    }, {
        "answer": "Line",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Queue"
    }, {
        "answer": "Apartment",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Flat"
    }, {
        "answer": "Cookie",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Biscuit"
    }, {
        "answer": "Truck",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Lorry"
    }, {
        "answer": "Sneakers",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Trainers"
    }, {
        "answer": "Diaper",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Nappy"
    }, {
        "answer": "Exit",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Way Out"
    }, {
        "answer": "Drunk",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Pissed"
    }, {
        "answer": "Lawyer",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Barrister"
    }, {
        "answer": "Pharmacy",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Chemist"
    }, {
        "answer": "Zee",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Zed"
    }, {
        "answer": "Hood",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Bonnet (car)"
    }, {
        "answer": "Thanks",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Ta"
    }, {
        "answer": "Complain",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Whinge"
    }, {
        "answer": "Period",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Full Stop"
    }, {
        "answer": "Baked Potato",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Jacket Potato"
    }, {
        "answer": "Second Floor",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "First Floor"
    }, {
        "answer": "Main Street",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "High Street"
    }, {
        "answer": "Muffler",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Silencer (car)"
    }, {
        "answer": "Bumper Cars",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Dodgems"
    }, {
        "answer": "Crosswalk",
        "category": "British Words Quiz",
        "question": "Zebra Crossing"
    }],
    "quizLength": 26,
    "title": "British Words Quiz",
    "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/british-words-quiz.php"
}